{
"question": "冷たい",
"answer": "つめたい"
},
{
"question": "青い",
"answer": "あおい"
},
{
"question": "吹く",
"answer": "ふく"
},
{
"question": "頁",
"answer": "ページ"
},
{
"question": "奥さん",
"answer": "おくさん"
},
{
"question": "引く",
"answer": "ひく"
},
{
"question": "段々",
"answer": "だんだん"
},
{
"question": "習う",
"answer": "ならう"
},
{
"question": "彼処",
"answer": "あそこ"
},
{
"question": "狭い",
"answer": "せまい"
},
{
"question": "軽い",
"answer": "かるい"
},
{
"question": "脱ぐ",
"answer": "ぬぐ"
},
{
"question": "万-1",
"answer": "まん"
},
{
"question": "煩い",
"answer": "うるさい"
},
{
"question": "並ぶ",
"answer": "ならぶ"
},
{
"question": "吸う",
"answer": "すう"
},
{
"question": "詰らない",
"answer": "つまらない"
},
{
"question": "閉まる",
"answer": "しまる"
},
{
"question": "咲く",
"answer": "さく"
},
{
"question": "真っ直ぐ",
"answer": "まっすぐ"
},
